[
  {
  "question": "What do you call a kid who doesn’t believe in Santa?",
  "answer": "A rebel without a Claus."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call an elf who sings?",
  "answer": "A wrapper!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call a broke Santa?",
  "answer": "Saint-nickel-less."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call a snowman in the summer?",
  "answer": "A puddle."
  },
  {
  "question": "How is Drake like an elf?",
  "answer": "He spends all his time wrapping!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call a greedy elf?",
  "answer": "Elfish."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call a snowman with a six pack?",
  "answer": "An abdominal snowman."
  },
  {
  "question": "What did Adam say on the day before Christmas?",
  "answer": "It’s Christmas, Eve!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What song do you sing at a snowman's birthday party?",
  "answer": "Freeze a jolly good fellow."
  },
  {
  "question": "What's worse than a reindeer with a runny nose?",
  "answer": "A snowman with a fever!"
  },
  {
  "question": "Who is never hungry at Christmas?",
  "answer": "The turkey — he’s always stuffed."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you get when you cross ice and Christmas?",
  "answer": "A cold Christmas!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What did one Christmas tree say to another Christmas tree?",
  "answer": "Lighten up!"
  },
  {
  "question": "How does a snowman lose weight?",
  "answer": "He waits for the weather to get warmer!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What did one snowman say to the other snowman?",
  "answer": "Do you smell carrots?"
  },
  {
  "question": "How did the ornament get addicted to Christmas?",
  "answer": "He was hooked on trees his whole life."
  },
  {
  "question": "What's every parent's favorite Christmas Carol?",
  "answer": "Silent Night."
  },
  {
  "question": "How is Christmas exactly like your job?",
  "answer": "You do all the work and some fat guy in a suit gets all the credit."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why did Frosty's wife ask for a divorce?",
  "answer": "He was a total flake."
  },
  {
  "question": "What kind of Christmas present just can’t be beat?",
  "answer": "A broken drum — you just can’t beat it!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What did the stamp say to the Christmas card?",
  "answer": "Stick with me and we’ll go places!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What’s the best thing to put in your Christmas dinner?",
  "answer": "Your teeth!"
  },
  {
  "question": "Why did the Christmas tree go to the barber?",
  "answer": "It needed to be trimmed."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why do reindeer like Beyoncé so much?",
  "answer": "She sleighs."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why do Christmas trees like the past so much?",
  "answer": "Because the present’s beneath them."
  },
  {
  "question": "What is green, covered in Christmas lights and Christmas bulbs, and goes ribbit?",
  "answer": "A mistle-toad."
  },
  {
  "question": "Jack Frost and Frosty the Snowman have a lot in common, but do you know what?",
  "answer": "They both have very chilly personalities."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why did the Grinch go to the liquor store?",
  "answer": "He was searching for some holiday spirit."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why did Jack Frost go to the doctor?",
  "answer": "He was coughing up snowballs."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why did the elf push his bed into the fireplace?",
  "answer": "He wanted to sleep like a log."
  },
  {
  "question": "How many letters are in the Christmas alphabet?",
  "answer": "25. There's 'noel'."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why is the Grinch such a good gardener?",
  "answer": "He has a green thumb."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you get when you cross a pig and Christmas tree lights?",
  "answer": "A piglet!"
  },
  {
  "question": "Did you hear about when Santa got stuck in the chimney?",
  "answer": "He was feeling a bit Claus-trophobic."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do you call an elf that just won the lottery?",
  "answer": "Welfy."
  },
  {
  "question": "What do reindeer say before they tell a joke?",
  "answer": "This one will sleigh you!"
  },
  {
  "question":"What do snowman do on the weekend?",
  "answer": "Chill!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What do grapes sing at Christmas?",
  "answer": "Tis the season to be jelly."
  },
  {
  "question": "How does Darth Vader enjoy his Christmas Turkey?",
  "answer": "On the dark side."
  },
  {
  "question": "Why is it always so cold around Christmastime?",
  "answer": "Because it's Decembrrrrrr."
  },
  {
  "question": "What’s white and goes up?",
  "answer": "A confused snowflake."
  },
  {
  "question": "What did Adam say on the day before Christmas?",
  "answer": "It's Christmas, Eve!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What goes 'Oh, Oh, Oh'?",
  "answer": "Santa walking backwards!"
  },
  {
  "question": "What is it called when a snowman has a temper tantrum?",
  "answer": "A meltdown."
  }
]